<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PTDS</string>
    <string name="ptds_image">ptds image</string>
    <string name="ptds_test_2">Post-traumatic stress disorder\n diagnostic and consultation system</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="self_test">Self Diagnostic</string>
    <string name="contact_doctor">Consult Doctor</string>
    <string name="daily_tips">Daily tips</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="exercise_n_routine">Exercise \n Routine</string>
    <string name="hello_welcome_to_ptds_diagnostic_system">Hello !! Welcome to PTDS Diagnostic system !!</string>
    <string name="section_a">Section A</string>

    <string name="section_a_instruction"><b>Instructions:</b> This questionnaire asks about problems you may have had after a very stressful experience involving
actual or threatened death, serious injury, or sexual violence. It could be something that happened to you directly,
something you witnessed, or something you learned happened to a close family member or close friend. Some
examples are a serious accident; fire; disaster such as a hurricane, tornado, or earthquake; physical or sexual attack or abuse; war; homicide; or suicide.\nFirst, please answer a few questions about your worst event, which for this questionnaire means the event that
currently bothers you the most. This could be one of the examples above or some other very stressful experience. Also, it could be a single event (for example, a car crash) or multiple similar events (for example, multiple stressful events in a war-zone or repeated sexual abuse).
    </string>
    
    <string name="worst_event_edt_label"><b>Briefly identify the worst event (if you feel comfortable doing so):</b>
    </string>
    <string name="how_long_ago_did_it_happen">How long ago did it happen?</string>
    <string name="please_estimate_if_you_are_not_sure">please estimate if you are not sure</string>
    <string name="did_it_involve_actual_or_threatened_death_serious_injury_or_sexual_violence">Did it involve actual or threatened death, serious injury, or sexual violence?</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="how_did_you_experience_it">How did you experience it?</string>
    <string name="it_happened_to_me_directly">It happened to me directly</string>
    <string name="i_witnessed_it">I witnessed it</string>
    <string name="i_learned_about_it_happening_to_a_close_family_member_or_close_friend">I learned about it happening to a close family member or close friend</string>
    <string name="i_was_repeatedly_exposed_to_details_about_it_as_part_of_my_job_for_example_paramedic_police_military_or_other_first_responder">I was repeatedly exposed to details about it as part of my job (for example, paramedic, police, military, or other first responder)</string>
    <string name="txt5">If the event involved the death of a close family member or close friend, was it due to some kind of accident or violence, or was it due to natural causes?</string>
    <string name="accident_or_violence">Accident or violence</string>
    <string name="natural_causes">Natural causes</string>
    <string name="not_applicable_the_event_did_not_involve_the_death_of_a_close_family_member_or_close_friend">Not applicable (the event did not involve the death of a close family member or close friend)</string>
    <string name="text_here">text here</string>
</resources>

